

- kaleb22@hotmail.com
- Santo Andre, SP
- www.linkedin.com/in/kalebdalla
- □ Brazilian
- 11989796023

Summary

I have almost 5 years of experience developing web applications. I have worked as a full stack developer for more than 3 years.

Medium Articles

my most common git commands

how to implement an e-mail service without a back-end in react

CSR vs SSR. Which one is the best?

how to dockerize a react back-end app and postgres

An intro to the Angular framework. Key concepts explained

RxJS — Why should you learn it?

Current Tech Stack

Angular
Java / Spring Boot
AWS Code Pipeline

GitLab

Jira

Postman

Languages

Portuguese

English

Certifications

CAF

Cambridge Advanced English

Kaleb Dalla Pria

Senior Software Engineer

Work experience

Senior Software Engineer

Since January 2022 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

My current position is focused in web development using Angular2+, Java/Spring and AWS services.

Software Engineer / Tech Lead

From May 2020 to December 2021 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

As a tech lead I was responsible for giving support to the other web and mobile devs of the team, designing technical solutions and planning new features.

Software Engineer

From January 2018 to May 2020 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

develop and implement products for Itau internet banking. I Worked with both backend and front-end development using mainlyn Java/SpringBoot, JavaScript, Jquery and AngularJs

Intern

From December 2016 to December 2017 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil Assist in the development of web applications for Itau internet banking.

Summer Internship

From June 2016 to August 2016 University of Southern California Los Angeles, United States

Assist the team of DeterLab in the area of network infrastructure.

Education

Computer Science

From June 2013 to May 2021 Universidade Federal do ABC Santo André, Brazil

Science and Technology

From May 2013 to January 2018 Universidade Federal do ABC Santo André, Brazil

Scholarship

From June 2015 to May 2016 Florida State University Tallahassee, United States Science Without Boarders - I studied two semesters of computer science at FSU

Skills

JavaScript

I have experience working with JavaScript and jQuery.

Angular

I'm currently working with this framework.

TypeScript

Java / Spring Boot

I have experience developing back-end for front-end applications with Java/Sping.

AngularJs

I worked in several projects using this framework.

Additional education

The Complete Web Developer in 2022

Since June 2022 Zero to Mastery Udemy

♦ Complete Angular Developer in 2022

From March 2022 to May 2022 Zero to Mastery Udemy

The Complete Junior to Senior Web Development RoadMap

From January 2020 to March 2020 Zero to Mastery Udemy